Hey guys, can you do me a favor? If you think that gay or trans people are an abomination,
can you just go ahead and unfollow me? If you think there's a gay agenda, can you go ahead
and unfollow me? If you use God as a reason to undermine why other people who do not harm
anybody should exist, can you go ahead and unfollow me? I ask this because I have a lot
going on today and I just, I don't have time to go through and individually block each of you
from my social media space who actually think these things. And I don't want you in my space
if you believe in a God that doesn't believe in loving people for being who they are who don't
harm people. So if y'all could do that, that would be like super helpful because I genuinely don't
have time and I honestly just don't want to hold space with people who have that kind of hate in
their heart. Okay, let me pack. Thank you.